[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film industry open and closed refer to what element of composition?", "correct_answer": "The frame", "incorrect_answers": ["Lighting", "Color", "Point of view"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You should always warm up your muscles before lifting weights.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the animated feature Aladdin released?", "correct_answer": "November 25, 1992", "incorrect_answers": ["June 10, 1993", "September 24, 1992", "April 14, 1991"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A mixture of water and honey can be used for what unconventional purpose?", "correct_answer": "Antifreeze for cars", "incorrect_answers": ["A treatment for throat infections", "A means of greasing a muffin pan", "Silver cleaner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before his death, host of the Tonight Show, Johnny Carson, used to meet Steve Martin, Chevy Chase and Carl Reiner in which club?", "correct_answer": "The Hollywood Gourmet Poker Club", "incorrect_answers": ["The Friars Club", "The Santa Monica Marina Club", "The Bel Air Golf and Country Club"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2005, there was a Burger King commercial for the Tendercrisp Bacon Cheddar Ranch sandwich that featured the lead singer of a famous band.  Which band was Darius Rucker in?", "correct_answer": "Hootie and the Blowfish", "incorrect_answers": ["King Crimson", "Pearl Jam", "Mike and the Mechanics"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In chemistry and physics, what do we call free radicals?", "correct_answer": "Atoms with at least one unpaired electron", "incorrect_answers": ["Atoms free of electrons", "Atoms not part of a molecule", "Atom freely floating in space"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jackass star Dave England has only one of which of the following body parts?", "correct_answer": "Testicle", "incorrect_answers": ["Big toe", "Arm", "Eye"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Green coffee beans stay acceptably fresh for how long?", "correct_answer": "Several years", "incorrect_answers": ["Several months", "Several days", "Several weeks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What candy bar was used in the 1985 movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "babyruth", "incorrect_answers": ["twix", "milkyway", "snickers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This substance is naturally present in water. It keeps the enamel strong and can stop or even reverse the process of tooth decay.", "correct_answer": "Fluoride", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrite", "Nitrate", "Chlorine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The risk of what type of cancer can be decreased by moderate wine consumption according to various studies?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Breast cancer", "Prostate cancer", "Lung cancer"]}]